shoppingblog.com 2019-05-30

# Writers Write, Inc. -- Privacy Policy

**Writers Write, Inc. Privacy Policy - Effective Date: July 1, 2015**  
Writers Write, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates ("Writers Write," "we," "us," "our") has developed this Privacy Policy to explain what and how we collect information from our users ("you"), and how we use this information. This Privacy Policy applies to your use of our websites, mobile websites, and any related services ("Service(s)") which are part of the Writers Write Lifestyle Network. This Privacy Policy does not govern our use of any information you provide to us when you call us, write to us, or communicate with us in any manner other than through the Services. This Privacy Policy may be modified over time. When the Policy is changed, the date will change at the top of the page. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically to keep updated about new practices. By using the Services, you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**Automatically Collected Information**

When you visit our websites, our mobile websites or use our Services, we automatically collect the following: IP address, browser type, language setting, operating system type, the webpages you access, user agent, time stamp and an Identifier for Advertising if you are using an iOS device or an Android ID if you are using an Android device. The user data collected does not contain personally identifiable information. 

**Voluntarily Submitted Information**

If you choose to post a comment, enter a sweepstakes, survey or contest, or register for a Service, and or register to become a member of the Site and in the course of using the Services, you may voluntarily submit personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your account ("Personal Information") which we may collect. Personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, city, country, phone number, profile photo, social media user name (such as a Twitter user name) and email address. When you voluntarily submit Personal Information for publication or to make a public comment on one of our websites, your Personal Information will be available to other users. In order to safeguard your privacy, we recommend that you never submit private information in a comment or other public manner. 

**International Transfer**

Writers Write processes its information in the United States. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, you consent to the transfer and storage of your information in the United States. The privacy laws in the United States may be different than those in your home country. 

**Use of Information Collected**

We may use the information we collect to administer and improve our Services, diagnose issues with our software and servers, gather demographic information, prevent fraudulent, illegal or unauthorized activity and any other lawful purpose consistent with this Privacy Policy. Third party advertising networks provide us with reports that detail ad displays, metrics and user behavior, but such reports do not personally identify any user. 

**How Your Information Is Shared**

Advertisers, third party ad networks, affiliates, service providers, database providers, agents and ad agencies may collect information from users in order to provide the Services to users, facilitate operation of the Services, provide security and technical services, track advertising effectiveness and tailor ads to users. 

We may share or transfer your information to third parties during negotiations regarding any sale, acquisition, financing or related business transfers or transactions. 

**Risk Reduction and Legal Process**

We may access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that a) we are required to so by law or legal process; b) that we believe is necessary to protect or defend us, our property, our rights or those of our users or third parties; or c) to protect against misuse of the Services. 

**Other**

We also share information about our audience in aggregate or anonymized form. Nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to restrict our use or sharing of aggregated or anonymized information in any way. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Our webpages may contain a small data file identifier called a cookie and small, invisible graphic images called a web beacon, pixel or pixel tag ("Web Beacons"). We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies and Web Beacons to create usage analytics reports, deliver advertising to users and provide content and advertising personalization. Web Beacons allow ad networks and service providers to provide aggregated and anonymized reports for us and for advertisers. 

**Social Plugins**

We use social plugins as part of our Services. We may use social plugins and/or embeds from social networks and sharing services such as Twitter, Facebook, Google+, Pinterest, Instagram, Vimeo and Youtube. Those plugins use icons such as Like, Comment, Share, Embed or Recommend. These plugins utilize cookies to transmit your data to the social network. For example, if Like a post on Facebook, that information is transferred to Facebook by your browser. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy policies of the social networks and sharing websites you use to understand how your information is used and shared by said networks. This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of these third parties. 

**Third Party Advertising and Analytics**

Some of the advertisements you see on our Services are delivered by third parties who collect information about your online activities on our Services through the use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and other technologies. We also use third parties to provide statistical information and analysis about usage of the Services. These third parties may also use Cookies, Web Beacons and other technologies to generate traffic and advertising usage reports. We may utilize certain services provided by Google/DoubleClick, Inc. ("DoubleClick"). For further information concerning DoubleClick's privacy practices, including the ability to opt-out from any data collection, reporting and/or targeting activities associated with its services, please [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

**Credit Card Information**

If you purchase advertising on our sites, we may require that you submit credit card information. By submitting your credit information through our Services, you expressly consent to the sharing of your information with payment processors and financial institutions who help complete the transaction. 

We use Paypal for credit card processing. We do not store your complete credit card account information, nor do we have direct control over or responsibility for your credit card account information. Paypal may store your credit card account information. Paypal uses state of the art technology and procedures to help protect your credit card information. 

**Links**

Our Services may contain links to other websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any linked websites or webpages. We explicitly disclaim responsibility for any content or actions of any linked website. We urge you to review the privacy practices of any website you visit before submitting any personal information. 

**Security**

We use reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of information collected and maintained through our Services. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized persons or hardware or software failure. 

**Do Not Track**

At this time we do not respond to web browser "Do Not Track" signals. 

**Children's Privacy**

The Services are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We urge parents and guardians to pay close attention to the online activities of children.
